

# **CONTACT**

Panten, Indonesia

in linkedin.com/in/juwono136

www.github.com/Juwono136

# **SKILLS**

HTML & CSS - Intermediate

Javascript - Intermediate

Node JS - Intermediate

MongoDB - Intermediate

**SQL** - Intermediate

React JS - Intermediate

Tensorflow - Intermediate

Python - Intermediate

Google Cloud Platform - Basic

# LANGUAGES

English - Intermediate

Japanese - Intermediate

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Japanese Language Proficiency Test (JLPT) N4 - The Japan Foundation

**Complete English Course** - Kampung Inggris

Responsive Web Design - FreeCodeCamp

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - <u>FreeCodeCamp</u>

Mathematics for Machine Learning Specialization - Coursera

Google IT Automation with Python Specialization - Coursera

**DeepLearning.AI TensorFlow Developer Specialization** - Coursera

**TensorFlow: Data and Deployment Specialization** - Coursera

# **JUWONO**

# FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER, MACHINE LEARNING ENTHUSIAST AND INTERMEDIATE JAPANESE TEACHER

## **SUMMARY**

Experienced in Full Stack Web and Intermediate Japanese Teacher with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry and school. Skilled in Educational Technology, Machine Learning Enthusiast, Japanese Language Intermediate, and Web Development.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### June 2015 - June 2016

#### PT Bank Central Asia Tbk

Staff Administrator Intern at Biro Pengetahuan dan Pengembangan Kualitas (PPK)

Job Description:

- Updating and reimbursing BCA employee scholarships.
- Schedule meetings with overseas training participants.
- Create and prepare payment memos.

#### August 2016 - September 2017

#### Ruangguru.com

Science Teacher on Digital Bootcamp Program

Job Description:

- Teaching Physic, Chemistry, and Math for Senior High School Student.

#### February 2018 - April 2022

SMPS Fioretti (Fioretti Junior High School)

**ICT Teacher and Japanese Teacher** 

Job Description:

- I teach IT Preneur, Computer Graphic Design and Basic Japanese Language.
- Apart from teaching, I also worked as a Head of The Computer Laboratory in SMPS Fioretti. My job is responsible to maintain computers and the inventories, recapitulate the items in the laboratory, design and repairing the computer networks at school.
- Sometimes teaching and training other teachers about how to use a technology/ICT.

#### February 2021 - Present

SMA Citra Berkat Tangerang (Citra Berkat Senior High School) Japanese Teacher and ICT Teacher

Job Description:

- I teach Basic Japanese Language from grade 10 to 12.
- I teach ICT (Information and Communication Technology) for grade 10.

## **EDUCATION**

May 2012 - June 2014

Science (Senior High School) SMA Bethel Kosambi

#### February 2018 - August 2023

Bachelor of Computer Science Pamulang University

#### February 2022 - July 2022

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka Machine Learning Path